BRITTANY HUBER

PRODUCT SUPPORT SPECIALIST

☑ brittanyleighhuber@gmail.com ③ brittanyhuber.com ふ 303-960-7370 ♀ Aurora, CO

in brittany-huber-6217ba139/ 🗘 bhuber23

SUMMARY

Product Support Specialist currently enrolled in the University of Denver Full Stack Web Development bootcamp. Background in technical troubleshooting, along with the following programming languages or frameworks: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap CSS, Javascript, jQuery, Node.js, Express.js, Handlebars, MySQL, Sequelize, and MongoDB

EMPLOYMENT

Mar. 2019 to Current RE/MAX, LLC · Product Support Specialist · Denver, CO

As a Product Support Specialist, I support the RE/MAX membership with any technical issues experienced with the products provided to RE/MAX affiliates, including issues with login credentials, data syndication, HTML discrepancies, and issues preventing the CRM from working as designed. I troubleshoot the bugs and issues experienced and collaborate with development teams to help determine trends and widespread problems. Using Salesforce, I manage the incoming tickets through a variety of channels and ensure cases are being resolved in a timely manner.

Apr. 2017 to Mar. 2019 Zillow Group · Client Engagement Specialist · Denver, CO

In my role as a Client Engagement Specialist I would connect consumers with real estate agents who had inquired about homes on the Zillow Group websites. Because of my expertise and overall success, I was also a member of the SOP Advisory Board in which I would help draft and develop standard operating procedures for our department to adhere to. The role involved some troubleshooting aspects in which I would assist both agents and consumers with issues they'd experience and when necessary escalate the issues to the appropriate departments.

Sept. 2013 to Nov.

Sunglass Hut · Sales Manager · Lone Tree, CO

As a Sales Manager, I helped ensure that all sales goals for the store were met or exceeded. I managed other staff members to help meet their goals while exceeding my personal goals for one of the top performing stores in the region. In addition to this, I maintained store paperwork to comply with company audits and ensured operational excellence.

EDUCATION

Sept. 2019 to Current University of Denver - Full Stack Bootcamp

Aug. 2007 to May University of Colorado - Boulder

SKILLS

TOOLS & TECHNOLOGIES HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, Node.js, MySQL, Sequelize, Express.js, Salesforce, Zendesk,

MongoDB, Handlebars

PROJECTS

Jan. 2020 to Feb. 2020 Fridge Friend

Fridge Friend is a full stack web application using Node.js, Express.js, jQuery, MySQL, Sequelize, Passport.js, and Handlebars that allows users to create an account and add the ingredients they have on hand in their kitchen to be stored in a database and then retrieve recipes based on those ingredients using the Spoonacular API to retrieve the recipe data.